<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2019-10-02T13:54:38+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Worst Practice</title><subtitle></subtitle><author><name>Gábor Iván</name></author><entry><title type="html">What am I doing???</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/general/what_am_i_doing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What am I doing???" /><published>2019-09-26T16:23:00+02:00</published><updated>2019-10-01T09:31:03+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/general/what_am_i_doing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/general/what_am_i_doing.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;i-cannot-explain-the-why&quot;&gt;I cannot explain the why&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;For a long time now I always felt I want to shout out to the world all the crazy ideas I have in my mind.
        But also I am full with fear. Lots of fear, because writing articles and publish them to the public is a
        huge responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;What if I write something rubbish, because English is not my mother tongue?&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;What if I write something absolutely wrong because I was too lazy to read a book in the given topic?&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;What if I write something totally bullshit that ruins my prestige to a level where nobody will ever count with me again?&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Writing a blog is a double-edged weapon.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;h2 id=&quot;what-will-i-present-here&quot;&gt;What will I present here?&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Tips and tricks. Ideas and workarounds. Smart and stupid solutions. Tutorials for the dummy me, to have them later 
        when I need them. And of course, it would be amazing if someone else other than me would find these articles useful too.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;To fulfill this goal I will try my best to entertain You. I will try to explain every detail of my ideas, and present not only 
        code samples but also links to the working source codes.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I had some private projects in the past that were really good to train myself, but they mostly remained unfinished. 
        My plan is to atomize these projects as much as possible, and create standalone modules and libraries, then publish 
        them here one-by-one.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I don’t say, that I am a top programmer with super-human knowledge in every programming language or technology. I know
        what I know, and I’d like to share my experiences. And I hope you welcome them. And You - dear visitor - can correct 
        me, and judge me any time.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Gábor Iván</name></author><category term="general" /><category term="personal" /><summary type="html">It like a professional suicide. I decided to share my thoughts in various IT-related topics. Maybe a good idea, maybe not. The people of the Internet will judge me.</summary></entry></feed>